<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"> <id>/</id><title>vCarbs.com</title><subtitle>A technology blog focused on cloud, automation and digital transformation.</subtitle> <updated>2021-05-25T10:46:57-07:00</updated> <author> <name>Nick Carbone</name> <uri>/</uri> </author><link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="/feed.xml"/><link rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" href="/"/> <generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator> <rights> © 2021 Nick Carbone </rights> <icon>/assets/img/favicons/favicon.ico</icon> <logo>/assets/img/favicons/favicon-96x96.png</logo> <entry><title>Amazon RDS on VMware – Part 3 – DB Provisioning</title><link href="/posts/RDS-on-VMware-Part3/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Amazon RDS on VMware – Part 3 – DB Provisioning" /><published>2021-01-05T00:00:00-08:00</published> <updated>2021-01-05T00:00:00-08:00</updated> <id>/posts/RDS-on-VMware-Part3/</id> <content src="/posts/RDS-on-VMware-Part3/" /> <author> <name>Nick Carbone</name> </author> <summary> Note: This is part 3 of a 3 part series. Part 1 || Part 2 || Part 3 Welcome to Part 3 of deploying RDS on VMware. In this post we are going to deploy a new MySQL RDS instance into our vSphere environment and connect it to an Ubuntu VM that will run WordPress. Navigating to our AWS RDS console, go ahead and click on Create database. A new page will pop up where we will input our data... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Amazon RDS on VMware – Part 2 – vSphere Cluster Onboarding</title><link href="/posts/RDS-on-VMware-Part2/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Amazon RDS on VMware – Part 2 – vSphere Cluster Onboarding" /><published>2020-12-30T00:00:00-08:00</published> <updated>2020-12-30T00:00:00-08:00</updated> <id>/posts/RDS-on-VMware-Part2/</id> <content src="/posts/RDS-on-VMware-Part2/" /> <author> <name>Nick Carbone</name> </author> <summary> Note: This is part 2 of a 3 part series. Part 1 || Part 2 || Part 3 Now that the prerequisites have been completed, we are ready to proceed with the deployment of RDS on VMware. Part 1 of the deployment can be viewed here. The first thing we are going to do is create a new resource pool within vCenter. This is where all of the RDS on VMware components will be deployed. Since this is... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Amazon RDS on VMware – Part 1 – Prerequisites</title><link href="/posts/RDS-on-VMware-Part1/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Amazon RDS on VMware – Part 1 – Prerequisites" /><published>2020-12-28T00:00:00-08:00</published> <updated>2020-12-28T00:00:00-08:00</updated> <id>/posts/RDS-on-VMware-Part1/</id> <content src="/posts/RDS-on-VMware-Part1/" /> <author> <name>Nick Carbone</name> </author> <summary> Note: This is part 1 of a 3 part series. Part 1 || Part 2 || Part 3 In this post I am going to cover the initial prerequisites for deploying Amazon RDS on VMware. I plan on writing additional posts that cover a new database deployment as well as migrating my Veeam database from a standalone Microsoft SQL Server to an Amazon RDS on VMware instance. Here is a link to the Amazon RDS on ... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Configuring the NetApp Simulator with Chef</title><link href="/posts/NetApp-Simulator-Chef/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Configuring the NetApp Simulator with Chef" /><published>2017-02-15T00:00:00-08:00</published> <updated>2017-02-15T00:00:00-08:00</updated> <id>/posts/NetApp-Simulator-Chef/</id> <content src="/posts/NetApp-Simulator-Chef/" /> <author> <name>Nick Carbone</name> </author> <summary> Late last year, I decided that I would try to automate the deployment of the NetApp Virtual Simulator. The organization I work for needed a method to easily and consistently deploy the simulator for customer demos and workshop sessions. Fortunately for me, Chef had already produced a cookbook that did exactly this, although I did run into a few issues getting it setup, which is why this blog po... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Ansible Tower &amp; vSphere Dynamic Discovery</title><link href="/posts/Ansible-Tower-vSphere-Discovery/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ansible Tower &amp; vSphere Dynamic Discovery" /><published>2017-02-07T00:00:00-08:00</published> <updated>2017-02-07T00:00:00-08:00</updated> <id>/posts/Ansible-Tower-vSphere-Discovery/</id> <content src="/posts/Ansible-Tower-vSphere-Discovery/" /> <author> <name>Nick Carbone</name> </author> <summary> It’s a new year, which means it’s time to learn new things! For the past 6 months, I’ve wanted to dive deeper into Ansible as a way to continuously force myself to write code in python. Naturally, I decided I would deploy Ansible Tower to monitor and manage my lab environment for changes and any configuration drift – there are two of us in the lab now, and we can’t afford to have any finger po... </summary> </entry> </feed>
